University Memorabilia Collection 1988.0026
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University Memorabilia Collection
undated, 1881-.
1988.0026
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
59.05 Linear feet
The collection contains ephemeral and artifactual materials created, collected, utilized, worn and/or associated primarily with students in conjunction with their experiences at or with the University of Connecticut.
Various.
History
In April 1881, the Connecticut General Assembly established the Storrs Agricultural School after accepting a gift of 170 acres of land, several frame buildings, and money from Charles and Augustus Storrs. The School opened on 28 September 1881, with twelve students in the first class. Before the turn of the century there were two name changes (Storrs Agricultural College1893, Connecticut Agricultural College1899). In 1933, two years after the institution celebrated its fiftieth anniversary, it became Connecticut State College, a name more in keeping with its steady advances and broadened mission. Six years later, in 1939, the General Assembly designated the institution the University of Connecticut, an acknowledgment of the institution's developing importance to the State in graduate and professional education, research and public service.
Additional details regarding student life, organizations and activities can be found in the UConn Chronology.
Scope and Content
The collection contains ephemeral and artifactual materials created, collected, utilized, worn and/or associated primarily with students in conjunction with their experiences at or with the University of Connecticut. The collection by no means completely documents activities at the institution since its establishment, but the materials do provide balance and depth to the understanding of student life and college experiences when utilized in conjunction with the official University administrative records.
Arrangement
The majority of the collection is arranged topically, although significant sections have been further divided by format.
Series I: Subject Files ( undated, 1889- ) include alphabetical and chronological files containing information on activities, events, organization, programs, policies, and other functions of University life. Similar materials may be found in different files. For example, dance programs can be found under this heading in this series but there are also dance programs in the fraternity/sorority files for the dances sponsored by these organizations. Memorabilia for the Greek organizations is dispersed in a similar fashion--materials may be found in Subject files as well as in Artifacts (paddles, jewelry, etc.) and Clothing.
Series II: Student Materials ( undated, 1881-1971 ) includes items (limited in number) pertaining to an individual's association with the institution. Class affiliation is included, when known, parenthetically.
Series III: Pins, Buttons and Patches ( undated, 1918-1998 ) contains official and unofficial pins and buttons produced by and associated with the institution and its divisions and departments.
Series IV: Scrapbooks ( undated, 1884-1981 ) have been organized into their own collection, regardless of provenance. A list of contributing individuals or entities in included in this finding aid.
Series V: Games and Toys ( undated, 1989-1992 ) contains University of Connecticut related games and toys marketed or distributed by organizations.
Series VI: Clothing ( undated, ca. 1895-2006 ) includes beanies, armbands, sweaters, jackets and similar items worn by students.
Series VII: Jewelry ( undated, ca. 1928-1955 ) includes momentos of college life with a direct UConn association.
Series VIII: Banners and Flags ( undated, 1918-1920s, 1943, 2003, 2006 ) includes a class banner and several associated with organizations or activities.
Series IX: Artifacts ( undated, 1891- ) contains objects used to commemorate events, activities or individuals, including commencement, class designation, reunions, and recent University marketing endeavors.
Series X: Commencement materials ( 1884- ) contains invitations, announcements, tickets and similar materials (not diplomas, see Series IX) associated with commencement ceremonies at the University. The Commencement Programs have been cataloged and are housed separately.
Series XI: 125th Anniversary ( 2006-2007 ) contains invitations, announcements, and a scrapbook associated with the year long celebration of the University's 125th anniversary. Cookie (with 125th logo) and fortune cookies were not retained. Materials separated from this series and housed elsewhere include UConn 125 Years, University of Connecticut 1881-2006 (C7630), two CDs, DVD, Founder's Day Tea photographs, Husky Dog design poster, giant crossword.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University's history. See especially, the papers of Robert F. Belden, A. J. Brundage, James R. Case, Fitts Family, Donald and Margaret Gaylord, Albert C. and Ralph D. Gilbert, Charles G. Hall, Lena Hurlburt, Howard Merrill, Lawrence F. Morico, A. J. Pierpont, Phil Samponaro, August Schulze, Lois Greene Stone, Randolph and Beatrice Whaples, and Stanley D. Woodmansee. Relevant administrative collections include the records of the Alumni Association, Departments, Board of Trustees, President's Office, the Commencement Collection, faculty papers and subject files. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection(s) and integrated into the larger University collection:
Random issues of the student newspaper; yearbooks; scrapbooks; commencement programs and invitations; periodicals produced by University departments, divisions or student groups; photographs; posters; media; and course bulletins.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Custodial History
Items in the collection may have orginally been offered to, held by or stored in other divisions of the University before final transfer to the University Archives.
Acquisition Information
Materials in the collection have been donated or transferred to, or otherwise acquired by, Archives & Special Collections over time. Donations and acquisitions containing more than a folder of personal materials have been maintained as separate, named collections, although ephemera and artifacts have been integrated into the Memorabilia Collection. See Related Materials for a list of these collections.
Connecticut Agricultural College.; Connecticut State College.; Storrs Agricultural College.; Storrs Agricultural School.; Storrs.; University of Connecticut.; Charms.; Correspondence.; Diaries.; Examinations.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Newsletters.; Notebooks.; Notes.; Obituaries.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Posters.; Publications.; School Records.; Storrs (Conn.); Stuffed toys.
- Series I: Subject Files, undated, 1889-
  - Activities
    - Entrance Examinations, 1899-1902 (Box 27:, Folder 311)
    - Freshman Week, 1939 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - Freshman Week, 1944 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
    - Hicks Prize Declamation Contest, 1916 (Box 43:, Folder 462)
    - Junior Week, 1917 (Box 43:, Folder 461)
    - Junior Week, 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - Junior Week, 1921 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
    - Junior Week, 1922 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
    - Junior Week, 1926 (Box 43:, Folder 485)
    - Junior Week, 1927 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - Junior Week, 1928 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - Junior Week, 1929 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Junior Weekend, 1955 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - Junior Weekend, 1957 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
    - Junior-Senior Banquet, 1919 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
    - Junior-Senior Banquet, 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - The Nutmeg, 1916 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
    - Pied Piper, 1948 (Box 27:, Folder 290)
    - Pig Roast, 1925 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Alumni
    - 10th Annual Reception of the Alumni Association, 1904 (Box 27:, Folder 300)
    - Association, undated, 1906 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1891, 25th Reunion, 1916 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1894, undated (Box 1:, Folder 17)
    - Class of 1916s, Banquet (Box 43:, Folder 465)
    - Class of 1920, 10th Reunion, 1930 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1916, 46th Reunion, 1962 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
    - Class of 1920, 35th Reunion, 1955 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
    - Class of 1927, 40th Reunion, 1967 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
    - Class of 1929, undated, 1989 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1929, Class Day Activities (Box 27:, Folder 299)
    - Sash, undated (Box 1:, Folder 23)
    - Reunion, Sigma Alpha Pi, 1918 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
  - Athletics
    - Association, undated (Box 1:, Folder 25)
      - Season ticket, 1920-1921 (Box 43:, Folder 504)
    - Baseball, undated, 1916, 1920-1921 (Box 1:, Folder 26)
    - Basketball, undated, 1918-1921, 1954 (Box 1:, Folder 27)
    - Basketball--Freshman, 1928 (Box 43:, Folder 484)
    - Basketball--Fan Software, 2003-2005 (Box 54)
    - Basketball--Men's NCAA Championship, 1999 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
    - Basketball, Women's--Championship tickets, 2001 (Box 62)
    - Field Day--Second Annual, 1895 (Box 27:, Folder 318)
    - Football, undated, 1916, 1921, 1924, 1927, 1928, 1965, 1966, 1998, 2008 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
    - Football Banquet, 1922 (Box 1:, Folder 30)
    - Receipt (blank), undated (Box 1:, Folder 31)
    - Schedule, undated, 1929, 1941-1942 (Box 1:, Folder 32)
    - Soccer, 2000 (Box 62)
    - Track, 1925 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
    - Varsity Letter certificates (Women), 1927-1929 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
    - Volleyball, 2000-2001 (Box 62)
  - Calendar, 1917-1918 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
  - Calendar, 1923 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1:, Folder 37)
  - Clippings (Pikowsky), undated (Box 53, Box 52:, Folder 530)
  - Clubs
    - 4-H, 1941, 1943, 1955-1956 (Box 1:, Folder 38)
    - Ag, 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 39)
    - Black Triumvirate, 1951 (Box 1:, Folder 40)
    - C.A.C., undated (Box 1:, Folder 41)
    - Dance and Dramatic
      - undated (Box 1:, Folder 42)
      - 1916 (Box 1:, Folder 43)
      - 1917 (Box 1:, Folder 44)
      - 1918 (Box 1:, Folder 45)
      - 1919 (Box 1:, Folder 46)
      - 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 47)
    - Fleur de Lis, 1901-1903 (Box 1:, Folder 48)
    - Home Economics (Box 1:, Folder 49)
    - Outing, 1946 (Box 27:, Folder 322)
    - Shakespearean, 1898-1926 (Box 1:, Folder 50)
    - Social Committee, undated, 1927 (Box 1:, Folder 51)
    - Social Satellites, 1919, 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 52)
    - Town and Gown, 1935-1940 (Box 27:, Folder 321)
    - University Christian Association, 1945-1946 (Box 27:, Folder 323)
  - Dance Cards
    - Midsummer Dance, 1906 (Box 1:, Folder 65)
    - Military Ball, 1915 (Box 1:, Folder 66)
    - Junior Hop, 1917 (Box 1:, Folder 67)
    - Mid-Year Informal, 1917 (Box 1:, Folder 68)
    - Military Ball, 1918 (Box 1:, Folder 69)
    - Spring Informal, 1918 (Box 1:, Folder 70)
    - Football Hop, 1919 (Box 1:, Folder 71)
    - Junior Informal, 1919 (Box 1:, Folder 72)
    - Junior Promenade, 1919 (Box 1:, Folder 73)
    - Junior Prom, 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 74)
    - Leap Year Dance, 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 75)
    - Mid-Year Informal, 1921 (Box 1:, Folder 76)
    - Football Hop, 1924 (Box 1:, Folder 77)
    - Football Hop, 1925 (Box 1:, Folder 78)
    - Hallowe'en Masked Frolic, 1925 (Box 1:, Folder 79)
    - Inter-Fraternity, 1925 (Box 1:, Folder 80)
    - Junior Prom, 1925 (Box 1:, Folder 81)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1926 (Box 1:, Folder 82)
    - Junior Prom, 1926 (Box 1:, Folder 83)
    - Varsity Club Dance, 1926 (Box 1:, Folder 84)
    - Co-Ed Prom, 1927 (Box 1:, Folder 85)
    - Junior Prom, 1928 (Box 1:, Folder 86)
    - Junior Prom, 1930 (Box 27:, Folder 319)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1931 (Box 1:, Folder 87)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1932 (Box 1:, Folder 88)
    - Junior Prom, 1932 (Box 1:, Folder 89)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 90)
    - Junior Prom, 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 91)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1934 (Box 1:, Folder 92)
    - Football Hop, 1934 (Box 1:, Folder 93)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1935 (Box 1:, Folder 94)
    - Junior Prom, 1935 (Box 1:, Folder 95)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1936 (Box 1:, Folder 96)
    - Military Ball, 1936 (Box 1:, Folder 97)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1937 (Box 1:, Folder 98)
    - Football Hop, 1938 (Box 27:, Folder 309)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1938 (Box 1:, Folder 99)
    - Military Ball, 1938 (Box 27:, Folder 310)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1939 (Box 27:, Folder 308)
    - Football Hop, 1939 (Box 1:, Folder 100)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1939 (Box 1:, Folder 101)
    - Junior Prom, 1939 (Box 27:, Folder 307)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1940 (Box 1:, Folder 102)
    - Football Hop, 1940 (Box 1:, Folder 103)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1940 (Box 1:, Folder 104)
    - Junior Prom, 1940 (Box 1:, Folder 105)
    - Semi-Formal, 1940 (Box 27:, Folder 305)
    - Spring Formal, 1940 (Box 27:, Folder 304)
    - Military Ball, 1940 (Box 1:, Folder 106)
    - Officer's Club, 1940 (Box 1:, Folder 107)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1941 (Box 1:, Folder 108)
    - Football Hop, 1941 (Box 1:, Folder 109)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1941 (Box 1:, Folder 110)
    - Junior Prom, 1941 (Box 1:, Folder 111)
    - Military Ball, 1941 (Box 1:, Folder 112)
    - Snow Ball, 1941 (Box 1:, Folder 113)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1942 (Box 1:, Folder 114)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1942 (Box 1:, Folder 115)
    - Junior Prom, 1942 (Box 1:, Folder 116)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1943 (Box 1:, Folder 117)
    - Junior Prom, 1943 (Box 1:, Folder 118)
    - Officer's Club, 1943 (Box 1:, Folder 119)
    - Military Ball, 1944 (Box 1:, Folder 120)
    - Football Hop, 1946 (Box 1:, Folder 121)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1947 (Box 1:, Folder 122)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1947 (Box 1:, Folder 124)
    - Semi-Formal Hop, 1947 (Box 1:, Folder 123)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1948 (Box 1:, Folder 125)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1948 (Box 27:, Folder 291)
    - Football Hop, 1949 (Box 27:, Folder 292)
    - Junior Prom, 1949 (Box 27:, Folder 293)
    - Military Ball, 1949 (Box 43:, Folder 501)
    - Co-Ed Formal, 1950 (Box 43:, Folder 503)
    - Coronation Ball, 1950 (Box 43:, Folder 502)
    - Junior Prom, 1950 (Box 27:, Folder 294)
    - Greek Letter Dance, 1951 (Box 1:, Folder 126)
    - Military Ball, 1951 (Box 1:, Folder 127)
    - Cinderella Ball, 1952 (Box 27:, Folder 329)
    - Football Hop, 1952 (Box 1:, Folder 128)
    - Froshmore Hop, 1952 (Box 27:, Folder 324)
    - Military Ball, 1952 (Box 1:, Folder 129)
    - Wing Cotillion, 1952 (Box 1:, Folder 130)
    - Junior Prom, 1953 (Box 27:, Folder 328)
    - 75th Anniversary Ball, 1956 (Box 1:, Folder 131)
    - Winter Whirl, 1957 (Box 1:, Folder 132)
  - Events
    - 30th Anniversary, 1916 (Box 43:, Folder 464)
    - 40th Anniversary ribbon, 1921 (Box 43:, Folder 459)
    - 75th Anniversary, 1956 (Box 1:, Folder 53)
    - Armed Forces Day, 1951-1952 (Box 1:, Folder 54)
    - Armed Forces Day, 1953 (Box 43:, Folder 452)
    - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1916 June 11 (Box 43:, Folder 463)
    - Campaign UConn (Capital campaign), 2001 (Box 62)
    - Chancellor's Forum, 2001 (Box 62)
    - Cinderella Ball, 1951 (Box 1:, Folder 55)
    - Class Day, 1895 (Box 27:, Folder 317)
    - Class Day, 1919 (Box 1:, Folder 56)
    - Class Day, 1920 (Box 1:, Folder 57)
    - Class Day, 1921 (Box 1:, Folder 58)
    - Class Day, 1926 (Box 1:, Folder 59)
    - Class Day, 1928 (Box 1:, Folder 60)
    - Class Day, 1931 (Box 1:, Folder 61)
    - College Sing, 1916 (Box 1:, Folder 62)
    - Community Picnic, 1919 (Box 1:, Folder 63)
    - Convocation, 1990 (Box 43:, Folder 490)
    - Dad's Day, 1941 (Box 1:, Folder 64)
    - Dairy Judging, 1925 (Box 2:, Folder 134)
    - Day of Pride, 1990 (Box 43:, Folder 469)
    - Dedication--Engineering, W. Cross, Home Economics, Manchester, Sprague, Whitney, Wood Halls, 1942 (Box 27:, Folder 302)
    - Dedication--Hall Dormitory, 1926 (Box 2:, Folder 135)
    - Dedication--Health Center (Box 2:, Folder 136)
    - Eastern States Exposition--Cattle Show Ribbon, 1977 (Box 27:, Folder 313)
    - Eastern States Exposition--Cattle Show Ribbon, 1982 (Box 27:)
    - Eastern States Exposition--Cattle Show Ribbon, 1985 (Box 27:)
    - Farmer's Day, 1920 (Box 2:, Folder 137)
    - Farmer's Week, 1919 (Box 2:, Folder 138)
    - High School Day, 1919 (Box 2:, Folder 139)
    - High School Day, 1920 (Box 2:, Folder 140)
    - Inauguration-- George Works, 1929 (Box 2:, Folder 141)
    - Military Day, 1955 (Box 43:, Folder 453)
    - Military Day, 1956 (Box 43:, Folder 454)
    - Military Day, 1957 (Box 43:, Folder 455)
    - Military Day, 1965 (Box 43:, Folder 505)
    - Silver Anniversary Convocation, 1960 (Box 2:, Folder 142)
    - Tickets, undated, 1919-1920, 1942-1943 (Box 2:, Folder 143)
    - Winter Carnival, 1953 (Box 2:, Folder 144)
    - Winter Carnival, 1954 (Box 43:, Folder 456)
    - Winter Weekend, 1960, 1962 (Box 43:, Folder 457)
    - UConn 2000 and 21st Century UConn, 1996, 2001 (Box 64)
      Scope and Content Note
      [Subjects include: copies of House Bill no. 6003 (An Act Concerning 21st Century UConn), a program overview for 21st Century UConn, and a photgraph.]
  - Forms
    - Extra Hours, undated (Box 2:, Folder 145)
    - Food Analysis Tag, circa 1920 (Box 43:, Folder 489)
    - Library Fines, undated (Box 43:, Folder 470)
    - Student Fees, 1914-1916, 1925 (Box 2:, Folder 146)
    - Examination book (blank), undated (Box 64)
  - Fraternities
    - Alpha Gamma Rho, 1926-1942 (Box 2:, Folder 148)
    - Alpha Phi, 1940, 1943 (Box 2:, Folder 149)
    - Alpha Phi Omega: Community Chess Carnival Letterhead, 1953 (Box 52:, Folder 531)
    - Beta Sigma Gamma, 1951 (Box 2:, Folder 150)
    - Delta Sigma, 1952 (Box 2:, Folder 151)
    - Delta Sigma, 1952 (Box 27:, Folder 325)
    - Eta Lambda Sigma, undated, 1920, 1926, 1939-1942 (Box 2:, Folder 152)
    - Phi Epsilon Pi, 1943 (Box 2:, Folder 153)
    - Phi Mu Delta, 1924, 1952 (Box 2:, Folder 155)
    - Rushing Rules, 1916, 1918-1919 (Box 2:, Folder 156)
    - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1952 (Box 27:, Folder 295)
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1951 (Box 2:, Folder 157)
    - Sigma Alpha Pi, 1916-1928, 1950 (Box 2:, Folder 158)
    - Sigma Alpha Pi/Alpha Gamma Rho, 1923-1924, 1941 (Box 2:, Folder 163)
    - Sigma Phi Gamma, 1940-1942 (Box 2:, Folder 166)
    - Tau Epsilon Phi, undated, 1952 (Box 2:, Folder 167)
    - Theta Chi, undated, 1950 (Box 2:, Folder 168)
  - Identification, undated (Box 2:, Folder 169)
  - Internet Access, 199? (Box 2:, Folder 170)
  - Parking, 1953, 2000, 2003-2004, 2006-2008 (Box 2:, Folder 171)
  - Programs and Invitations
    General note
    [Invitations associated with commencement activities are filed with the commencement materials.]
    - undated (Box 2:, Folder 172)
    - 1898 (Box 62)
    - 1916 (Box 2:, Folder 173)
    - 1919 (Box 2:, Folder 174)
    - 1920 (Box 2:, Folder 175)
    - 1921 (Box 2:, Folder 176)
    - 1922 (Box 2:, Folder 177)
    - 1924 (Box 27:, Folder 452)
    - 1925 (Box 2:, Folder 178)
    - 1926 (Box 27:, Folder 301)
    - 1934 (Box 2:, Folder 179)
    - 1936 (Box 2:, Folder 180)
    - 1940 (Box 27:, Folder 306)
    - 1943 (Box 2:, Folder 181)
    - 1944 (Box 2:, Folder 182)
    - 1945 (Box 2:, Folder 183)
    - 1946 (Box 2:, Folder 184)
    - 1948 (Box 2:, Folder 185)
    - 1949 (Box 27:, Folder 296)
    - 1950 (Box 2:, Folder 186)
    - 1951 (Box 2:, Folder 187)
    - 1952 (Box 2:, Folder 188)
    - 1953 (Box 2:, Folder 189)
    - 1954 (Box 2:, Folder 190)
    - 1955 (Box 2:, Folder 191)
    - 1956 (Box 2:, Folder 192)
    - 1957 (Box 2:, Folder 193)
    - 1959 (Box 2:, Folder 194)
    - 1966 (Box 2:, Folder 195)
    - 1991 (Box 27:, Folder 330)
    - 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 331)
    - 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 478)
    - 1998 (Box 43:, Folder 479)
    - 1999 (Box 43:, Folder 476)
    - 2000 (Box 43:, Folder 477)
    - 2001 (Box 43:, Folder 474)
    - 2002 (Box 43:, Folder 475)
    - 2003 (Box 43:, Folder 473)
    - 2004 (Box 43:, Folder 472)
    - 2005 (Box 43:, Folder 470)
    - 2006 (Box 43:, Folder 471)
    - 2007 (Box 62)
    - 2008 (Box 43:, Folder 506)
  - ROTC, 1920 (Box 2:, Folder 196)
  - Seals
    - ca. 1998 (Box 2:, Folder 197)
    - Access to Excellence (Wilbur Cross foamcore), undated (Box Shelf)
    - University of Connecticut (foamcore), ca. 1995 (Box Shelf)
  - Songs, undated, 1954 (Box 2:, Folder 198)
  - Sororities
    - Delta Chi, undated (Box 2:, Folder 199)
    - Delta Chi Omega, 1939-1942 (Box 2:, Folder 200)
    - Delta Epsilon Phi, 1953-1954 (Box 2:, Folder 201)
    - Delta Epsilon Phi, 1955-1956 (Box 27:, Folder 327)
    - Delta Pi, 1957-1965 (Box 2:, Folder 202)
    - Gamma Sigma, 1942 (Box 2:, Folder 203)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1943 (Box 2:, Folder 204)
    - Pi Beta Phi, 1942-1958 (Box 2:, Folder 154)
    - Theta Psi, 1938-1939 (Box 2:, Folder 205)
  - Sticker(s)
    - Alumni Association, undated (Box 1:, Folder 206)
    - Connecticut, undated (Box 27:, Folder 326)
    - Connecticut Aggies (no introduction), circa 1916 (Box 43:, Folder 466)
    - Connecticut State Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 27:, Folder 338)
    - UConn, undated (Box 62)
  - Stationery (University), undated (Box 43:, Folder 468)
  - Storrs Congregational Church, 1927-1928, 1941 (Box 2:, Folder 207)
  - Student Union, undated (Box 2:, Folder 208)
  - Student
    - Deportment Record, 1889-1890 (Box 2:, Folder 209)
    - Deportment Record, 1892-1893 (Box 2:, Folder 210)
    - Deportment Record, 1893-1894 (Box 2:, Folder 211)
    - Deportment Record, 1895-1896 (Box 2:, Folder 212)
    - Employment, undated (Box 2:, Folder 213)
    - Rules, undated (Box 2:, Folder 214)
- Series II: Student Materials, undated, 1881-2005
  - Abelman, Beatrice (1928), undated, 1918-1929 (Box 2:, Folder 215)
  - Alling, Roger L. (1943), undated, 1939-1940 (Box 2:, Folder 216)
  - Avery, B.T. (1916), 1910 (Box 2:, Folder 217)
  - Bierkan, John A., 1940 (Box 43:, Folder 486)
  - Bishop, Mark (1906), 1906, 1910, 1916 (Box 2:, Folder 218)
  - Boyle, Rosemary (1940) (Box 2:, Folder 219)
  - Brown, Benjamin A. (1916s, 1926), 1914-1916 (Box 43:, Folder 458)
  - Bulmer, Robert (1957), undated, 1952 (Box 2:, Folder 220)
  - Burk, Oliver G. (1932), 1928-1929 (Box 52:, Folder 517)
  - Burke, Carol, 1949-1950 (Box 43:, Folder 500)
  - Case, Frank D. (1882), 1881-1882, 1952 (Box 2:, Folder 221)
  - Case, James R. (1916), 1933, 1969-1971 (Box 2:, Folder 222)
  - Cowdell, Ruth (1922) (Box 2:, Folder 223)
  - Curtis, C.T. (1896), 1897 (Box 2:, Folder 224)
  - Donovan, Bessie (1906), 1902 (Box 2:, Folder 225)
  - Dow, Gardner (1919) (Box 2:, Folder 226)
  - Evans, John Harry (1896), undated, 1904 (Box 2:, Folder 227)
  - Filip, Ruth Bosworth, undated, 1954-1964 (Box 3:, Folder 228)
  - Freshman Year Experience (FYE), 2004-2005
    - FYE 182--Documentation of a day in the life of a freshman student by eleven members of FYE, 2004 (Box 29)
    - FYE 182--Documentation of a day in the life of a freshman student by eight members of FYE, 2005 (Oversize OS, Box 37)
  - Gaylord, Janet (1958), 1954-1957 (Box 3:, Folder 229)
  - Gray, Fred, 1951 (Box 43:, Folder 487)
  - Green, Arthur O., 1897 (Box 62)
  - Green, Charles R., 1892-1895 (Box 62)
  - Hotchkiss, Luella (1901), 1899-1900 (Box 3:, Folder 230)
  - Kalison, Harriet (1943), undated, 1943 (Box 3:, Folder 231)
  - Margolis, Henry (1931), undated, 1930-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 320)
  - Miles, Eunice Mentzer (1923), 1920-1948 (Box 3:, Folder 232)
  - Murphey, Horace (1928), 1924 (Box 3:, Folder 233)
  - Pikosky, Andrew C. (1947), undated, 1946-1947 (Box 3:, Folder 234)
  - Richter, Elsa (1932), undated, 1930 (Box 27:, Folder 297)
  - Saxton, Irene (1929), undated (Box 3:, Folder 235)
  - Scott, Dwight Japy (1920), undated, 1918-1919 (Box 3:, Folder 236)